[
  {
    "questionNo": 1,
    "question": "In 'Honkai Impact 3,' which organization do players join to combat the Honkai?",
    "options": ["Anti-Honkai Union", "Schicksal", "World Serpent"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 2,
    "question": "Who is the main character and leader of the Valkyries in 'Honkai Impact 3'?",
    "options": ["Kiana Kaslana", "Bronya Zaychik", "Mei Raiden"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 3,
    "question": "What type of creatures are the main antagonists in 'Honkai Impact 3'?",
    "options": ["Zombies", "Aliens", "Honkai Beasts"],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 4,
    "question": "Which weapon type does Rita Rossweisse primarily use in battles?",
    "options": ["Greatsword", "Sword and Shield", "Dual Pistols"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 5,
    "question": "What is the name of the city that serves as the main setting in 'Honkai Impact 3'?",
    "options": ["Tokyo", "New York", "St. Freya City"],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 6,
    "question": "Which character is known for wielding a scythe-like weapon and has a white bunny companion?",
    "options": ["Rita Rossweisse", "Theresa Apocalypse", "Kiana Kaslana"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 7,
    "question": "What is the primary energy source used to power battlesuits in 'Honkai Impact 3'?",
    "options": ["Electricity", "Ether", "Honkai Energy"],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 8,
    "question": "Which Valkyrie is associated with ice powers and uses a cross-shaped weapon?",
    "options": ["Rita Rossweisse", "Bronya Zaychik", "Kiana Kaslana"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 9,
    "question": "What is the name of the virtual AI assistant that guides players through the game's features?",
    "options": ["Aether", "Athena", "Mei Raiden"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 10,
    "question": "Which organization is responsible for creating and maintaining the battlesuits used by the Valkyries?",
    "options": ["Anti-Honkai Union", "Schicksal", "SCEL"],
    "correctOption": 2
  }
]
